Risto Tõldsep



ristotoldsep@gmail.com



56894570



linkedin.com/in/risto-t%C3%B5ldsep-241b76199



https://ristotoldsep.eu

Summary

I have graduated from Tallinn University of Technology with a Bachelor in Computer Systems Engineering.

Currently working full time as a web developer/designer, mainly focused on crafting intuitive and dynamic user experiences.

Feel free to get in touch with me. I am always open to discussing new projects, creative ideas or job opportunities.

Experience

Web Developer/Designer

vDesignly / vDisain
Jun 2021 - Present (1 year 4 months +)

all.

Freelance Web Developer

Freelance (Self employed)

Jan 2021 - Present (1 year 9 months +)

Working full-time as a freelance Wordpress Developer & specialising in e-commerce.

Founding Board Member

Romeo Tango OÜ

Sep 2019 - Present (3 years 1 month +)

DJ & event organizing services



Back Office Agent

International Personal Finance Plc

Jun 2019 - Sep 2020 (1 year 4 months)

I was part of a Fenno-Baltic Back Office team, where I was responsible for ensuring that our clients had a seamless, speedy and high-quality experience during the loaning process, which meant that I processed all customer related tasks that span the full customer journey, ranging from processing payments, handling customer verification tasks, keeping the database up to date, executing data analysis and undertaking administrative activities, such as investigative activities around payments, verifications and customer background checks.

Logistics Sergeant

Estonian Defense Forces

Jul 2018 - Jun 2019 (1 year)

Lead a group of 15 soldiers and was responsible for the logistics, management and transportation of heavy artillery munitions and military gear.

Education

🌠 TalTech – Tallinn University of Technology

Bachelor's degree, Computer Systems Networking and Telecommunications 2019 - 2022

Gustav Adolf Grammar School

High School Diploma, English-Mathematics 2015 - 2018

Lagedi Primary School

2006 - 2015

⊗[™] Zero To Mastery Academy

Web Development 2020 - Present

Licenses & Certifications

- Succeeding in Web Development: Full Stack and Front End LinkedIn
- in Strategic Thinking LinkedIn
- **Meb Programming Foundations** LinkedIn
- **Certificate in Advanced English (C1)** Cambridge University Press & Assessment **English** 17CEE0045112
- **in Mobile Marketing Foundations** LinkedIn
- in IT Security Foundations: Core Concepts LinkedIn
- **The Learning PC Maintenance and Performance** LinkedIn
- in IoT Foundations: Fundamentals LinkedIn
- DevOps Foundations: Lean and Agile LinkedIn
- **Build Your First React Website** Coursera

6PLAFPF3F4H2

- in Technology for Product Managers LinkedIn
- in Ethical Hacking with JavaScript LinkedIn
- in Web Development Foundations: Web Technologies LinkedIn
- The Web Developer Bootcamp Udemy UC-720130f1-19cd-4b62-b838-1285eead2da6
- Data Structures and Algorithms in C Udemy UC-ed5a22cb-2be5-4cb4-bb2d-bfee9d6eb35f
- The Complete Web Developer in 2021: Zero to Mastery Udemy UC-861f682f-0dba-4cc0-8174-dfd27c8b6b83
- WordPress Development: Unlocking Power With Code Udemy UC-f167cb90-297e-4e7f-99cd-9849b99468a2
- **E-Commerce with PHP & MySQL** Udemy UC-d9f642cd-60d7-4325-890e-acaac6d8d6d4
- The Javascript Course 2021 Udemy UC-aa1c7947-c2c6-4f69-bc4b-26f18a21ce0e/
- Social Network with PHP, MySQL, Javascript Udemy UC-a2c06be8-8f57-4e7e-9814-3af4a349ad4e

Skills

Back Office Operations • Teamwork • Event Management • Office Operations • Web Development • Full-Stack Development • Leadership • Strategic Thinking • Strategy • Front-End Development